able2know.org 2019-04-01

# able2know - Privacy Policy

## I. Your Privacy at Able2know

When registering at able2know you do not need to provide any information except for the bare minimum that we need for your account: a username, e-mail and a password. Unlike many other sites, we will never sell these e-mails to unscrupulous spammers. In fact, we won't sell or give e-mails to anyone, regardless of their scruples, unless we are ordered to do so by law.

We collect no personally identifying information about you when you visit our website unless you choose to provide this information to us.

There is nothing we know of that we can do to show more respect for your privacy, but if you have any suggestions on how we can improve our commitment to your privacy, please don't hesitate to contact us.

## II. What We Collect and Store Automatically

If you do nothing during your visit but browse through the website, read pages, or download information, we will gather and store certain information about your visit automatically. This information does not identify you personally. Rather, information is kept in the aggregate. We automatically collect and store only the information about your visit. We use the information we collect to understand the traffic to our site; for example, it's important to know how much bandwidth the site uses so that we can purchase more if needed; if the "hits" to our site increase, we need to pay more money for better hosting. This kind of information helps us make our site more useful to visitors like you.

## III. If You Send Us E-mail

You may choose to provide us with personal information, such as when you e-mail us with a comment or question. We use that information to improve our service to you or to respond to your request. Except for authorized law enforcement investigations, we do not share our e-mail with any other outside organizations.

## IV. Cookies

able2know uses cookies to allow users to have their computers remember their login information, preferences and other page details for them.

Google may use cookies to serve ads based on your prior visits to able2know.org. Google's use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to your based on your visits able2know.org and/or other sites on the Internet. You may opt out of the use of the Doubleclick cookie for interest based advertising by visiting <https://www.google.com/ads/preferences/>

## V. Links to Other Sites

Like most sites, able2know contains links to other websites. When you follow a link to another site, you are subject to the privacy policy of the new site.

## VI. Restriction of Liability

Able2know makes no claims, promises or guarantees about the accuracy, completeness, or adequacy of the contents of this website and expressly disclaims liability for errors and omissions in the contents of this website.

No warranty of any kind, implied, expressed or statutory, including but not limited to the warranties of non-infringement of third party rights, title, merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose and freedom from computer virus, is given with respect to the contents of this website or its hyperlinks to other Internet resources.

Reference in this website to any specific commercial products, processes, or services, or the use of any trade, firm or corporation name is for the information and convenience of the public, and does not constitute endorsement, recommendation, or favoring by Able2know.

Advertisements are subject to the Privacy Policy of the advertising site.
